db.questions.insertMany([
  {
    question_num: 1,
    question: "What legendary Pokemon did Ash see on the first day of his Pokemon journey?",
    type: "Multiple choice",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "Ho-oh",
    choices: ["Pikachu", "Ho-oh", "Articuno", "Lugia"] 
  },
  {
    question_num: 2,
    question: "What is Naruto's favorite food?",
    type: "Text answer",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "ramen"
  },
  {
    question_num: 3,
    question: "The Devil's Fruit that gave Luffy his powers is called the Flame-Flame Fruit.",
    type: "True or False",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question_num: 4,
    question: "Conan Edogawa's true identity is Shinichi Kudo.",
    type: "True or False",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question_num: 5,
    question: "What is Agumon's second digivolution form?",
    type: "Multiple choice",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "Greymon",
    choices: ["Garurumon", "Greymon", "Angemon", "Rosemon"]
  },
  {
    question_num: 6,
    question: "In the anime Fate Stay Night, what is Berserker's true name?",
    type: "Multiple choice",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "Heracles",
    choices: ["Lancelot", "Spartacus", "Frankenstein", "Heracles"]
  },
  {
    question_num: 7,
    question: "In the anime Death Note, what is L's real name?",
    type: "Text answer",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "L Lawliet"
  },
  {
    question_num: 8,
    question: "In the anime Danganronpa, the real mastermind behind the killing game is Enoshima Junko.",
    type: "True or False",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question_num: 9,
    question: "In the anime Fairy Tail, what is the name of Natsu's patron dragon?",
    type: "Multiple choice",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "Igneel",
    choices: ["Igneel", "Grandine", "Makarov", "Happy"]
  },
  {
    question_num: 10,
    question: "In the anime Kuroko's Basketball, what is the number on Taiga's Seirin jersey?",
    type: "Number answer",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: 10
  },
  {
    question_num: 11,
    question: "In the anime Love Live, the title of the song performed by Âµ's on Season 2 Episode 3 is Snow Halation.",
    type: "True or False",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "False"
  },{
    question_num: 12,
    question: "In the anime Your Lie in April, what day was Kousei's piano competition which was also the day Kaori passed away?",
    type: "Multiple choice",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "February 18",
    choices: ["February 18", "April 1", "December 14", "June 8"]
  },
  {
    question_num: 13,
    question: "In the anime Sword Art Online, how many survivors remained when Kirito completed SAO?",
    type: "Number answer",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: 6147
  },
  {
    question_num: 14,
    question: "In the anime Food Wars, what was the dish made by Erina Nakiri for the Breakfast Buffet Challenge on Season 1 Episode 13?",
    type: "Text answer",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "Eggs Benedict"
  },
  {
    question_num: 15,
    question: "In the anime Katekyo Hitman Reborn, who is founder of the Vongola Famiglia and was also known as Vongola Primo?",
    type: "Text answer",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Anime",
    answer: "Giotto"
  },
   {
    question_num: 16,
    question: "In Ben 10 Alien Force, which was the first alien that Ben was able to transform into?",
    type: "Text answer",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "TV Series",
    answer: "Swampfire"
  },
   {
    question_num: 17,
    question: "In which episode of Arrow Season 2 was Barry Allen's first appearance?",
    type: "Number answer",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "TV Series",
    answer: 8
  },
   {
    question_num: 18,
    question: "In The Flash Season 3, what is the true identity of Savitar?",
    type: "Multiple choice",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "TV Series",
    answer: "Barry Allen",
    choices: ["Eobard Thawne", "Hunter Zolomon", "Wally West", "Barry Allen"]
  },
   {
    question_num: 19,
    question: "In Adventure Time, what is the animal that can be seen somewhere in every episode?",
    type: "Text answer",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "TV Series",
    answer: "snail"
  }
])
